<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Wayist Spiritual Energy Centers</title>
	<atom:link href="https://wayist.com/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://wayist.com</link>
	<description>The Butterfly Path</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:41:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.6.10</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/2020-05-13.png</url>
	<title>Wayist Spiritual Energy Centers</title>
	<link>https://wayist.com</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Chakra &#038; kundalini therapy, alignment and balancing</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/chakra-kundalini-therapy-alignment-and-balancing/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=chakra-kundalini-therapy-alignment-and-balancing</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/chakra-kundalini-therapy-alignment-and-balancing/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:41:54 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=577</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[We do Soul Energy Therapy We do Soul Energy Therapy Therapist Jean du Plessis is a professional pneumatologist, and well known author of books on spirituality East and West. Jean is our resident therapist in Siem Reap, Cambodia. About A soul, is a subtle energy body that consists of live energy matter and organs of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h2>We do Soul Energy Therapy</h2>



<h1>We do Soul Energy Therapy</h1>



<h2>Therapist</h2>



<p><a href="https://wayist.com/index.php/component/content/?id=130&amp;Itemid=1683">Jean du Plessis</a> is a professional pneumatologist, and well known author of books on spirituality East and West. Jean is our resident therapist in Siem Reap, Cambodia.<img loading="lazy" src="https://wayist.com/images/download1.jpg" alt="soul field and aura healing in Siem Reap by Jean du Plessis author and pneumatologist" width="107" height="144"></p>



<h2>About</h2>



<p><strong>A soul, is a subtle energy body</strong> that consists of live energy matter and organs of different types. We are souls. We are ancient, and we have had many opportunities to incarnate (in-carnate: to go into flesh).</p>



<p><strong>A human body, is an organic body</strong> that consists of live organic matter and organs of different types. If you are reading this, then you are a soul presently incarnated in a human body. Human bodies are wondrous, yet they are fragile and do not last very long.</p>



<p><strong>The link between human body and the soul</strong>, is the human body-mind. The human mind is a subtle energy organ generated by the human brain. It’s lifespan and efficacy relies to the health and life of the brain. Body-minds try to deal with human experiences before the resulting wisdom is passed over to be permanently stored in soul minds.</p>



<p><strong>Soul Energy Therapy analyzes soul energies</strong> (often called, auras, kundalini, etc.) to determine whether conditions of the physical body, or human mind, negatively impact on one’s soul development-diagnosis. Treatment involves corrective actions, which may involve <img src="https://wayist.com/images/chakra-meditation.gif" alt="chakra meditation and healing in Cambodia therapist">natural therapies, lifestyle changes, mental re-programming, physical interventions, and counselling.</p>



<p><strong>Therapists can intervene in energy flows</strong> to some extent but this is not a long-lasting solution, and also it is not the purpose of this therapeutic discipline.</p>



<h2>What do we see?</h2>



<p>Captured in our four soul-minds (4 lower chakras) is the essence of who we are, as individuals. We are the culmination of many lifetimes of experiences. Our soul’s energies create the ‘picture’ of what we ‘look’ like to other soul and spiritual beings. From a human perspective, looking at a soul it to see who we really are—the real person.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://wayist.com/images/infra-1.jpg" alt="Infrared imaging soul energy healing pneumatology at Wayism center for spirituality"/></figure></div>



<p>However, we need to explain that we do not really see, we sense. A large percentage of therapists ‘see’ auras most of the time when they are in therapeutic mode. Nevertheless, because auras change as soul moods change, the visible aura is not the most reliable diagnostic tool. We do make use of Infrared thermal imaging scans sensitive to 0.1<sup>0</sup>&nbsp;Celcius for certain tests. The scans on left shows before and after treatment&#8211;a pleasing result.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://wayist.com/images/infra2.png" alt="Infrared thermography spiritual chakra aura therapy"/></figure></div>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><br><img src="https://wayist.com/images/themography-spiritual-counselling.jpg" alt="thermography spiritual counselling diagnostics">We have to run energy tests making use of various techniques. We do cross checks and double checks to finally get the full picture of the complex, multi-layered person you are. A diagnostic session may have the look / feel of a combination of reiki, psychoanalysis, aromatherapy and touch therapies (massage / acupressure / reflexology).</p>



<p>Just for interest sake&#8211;notice the breast scan on right, development of tumours in the left breast. Tumors demand increased blood flow and manifest a negative energy that a good therapist usually pics up.<em> Please&#8211;</em>we are not medical doctors and we do not do medical diagnoses. We will make you aware of issues if we notice them, but we are not medical practitioners.</p>



<h1>More About Kundalini Energy Therapy</h1>



<p>FYI. The term “Chakra Alignment” is a western misnomer that leads to popular misconceptions—exploited mostly in western cultures. Chakras are the minds of your soul body. They cannot go out of alignment, like a car&#8217;s wheels for example. You have seven major chakras one above the other. Chakras can be overworked, can become burdened with trauma, and may need help like any mind&#8211;but they cannot go out of alignment.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>What is the ancient art of Soul Energy Therapy?</h2>



<p class="has-text-align-center"><img loading="lazy" src="https://wayist.com/images/reiki1.jpg" alt="energy and healing session" width="156" height="157">Trained pneumatologists, practice the ancient art of soul energy healing.</p>



<p>Chakra therapy and prana / qi therapy, are aspects of the wider discipline. Reiki healing is a small part of this. We make use of various techniques to examine the energy flow through the subtle body and its chakras, for diagnostic purposes.</p>



<p>A successful diagnosis highlights several factors that disturb the health of soul. These factors may be related to mental attitude, culturally conditioned thinking, emotional ‘baggage’, physical anomaly or posture habits, dietary matters or persistent exposure to environmental factors that negatively impact one’s health of soul.</p>



<p>In summary: A pneumatologist investigates one’s soul energies to make a diagnosis of body, mind and soul issues that may require your attention. These conditions may impact soul development if not addressed.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">One cannot “align” subtle-body energies to cure a soul, but one can often remove factors that negatively impact soul health of soul.<img loading="lazy" src="https://wayist.com/images/chakra-chart1.jpg" alt="chakras and colors" width="202" height="244"></p>



<h2>What can I expect during a Spiritual Therapy session?</h2>



<p>Siem Reap Wayist Center therapy sessions are usually 45 to 60 minutes. Sometimes, it is possible to conduct more than one sessions per day.</p>



<p>A session may have the look-feel of a combination of Reiki, Psychoanalysis, Aromatherapy and touch therapies (massage /acupressure / reflexology).</p>



<h2>Will I feel better after a session?</h2>



<p>Patients usually experience a feeling of wellness after a treatment, because of several factors. However, the sense of well-being is often a temporary symptomatic relief, because the root problem(s) lies deeper and needs long-term attention. Nevertheless, once a root problem is identified, patients can usually continue along the healing path without the direct assistance of a therapist. The therapist’s task is to enable the patient on healing path.</p>



<h2><img src="https://wayist.com/images/eh-300x249.jpg" alt="Aura fields around the human body">Can a root problem(s) be identified in one session?</h2>



<p>It is not uncommon to identify a priority root issue in one session. However, the human body/mind/psyche interplay is very complex, and multi-layered.</p>



<h2>Do I need knowledge of soul energies and technical terms, for this to work?</h2>



<p>It is not required to have prior knowledge. You will however learn along the way because knowledge will empower you on the healing and maintenance path. You will learn about, or more about, concepts like prana, soul and spirit, body-mind and soul-minds, chakras, kundalini, sushumna, nadis, aura, how reincarnation and karma challenge your soul development and what you can do about it, and more.</p>



<p>Have your chakras re-energized, balanced and all minor chakras checked and tuned and a full aura scan to correct any imbalanaces you may have.</p>



<p>One stumbling block for patient and therapist alike, is when a patient has incorrect knowledge—an issue mostly prevalent among westerners.</p>



<h2>What is the fee for a Chakra Therapy session at Siem Reap Wayist Center?</h2>



<ul><li>How long it take: up to 60 min</li><li>When: By appointment</li><li>Where: <strong>Siem Reap Wayist Center</strong>&nbsp;&#8211; see <a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Wayist+Spiritual+Retreat/@13.3703347,103.865426,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x58935658e03e4579" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Location</a></li><li>For more information, please CONTACT US via <a class="" href="mailto:sr@wayist.com">sr@wayist.com</a> or <a href="tel:+85577804814">phone/ WhatsApp +85577804814</a></li></ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/chakra-kundalini-therapy-alignment-and-balancing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>4</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prana &#038; Reiki Chakra Balancing</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/prana-reiki-chakra-balancing/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=prana-reiki-chakra-balancing</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/prana-reiki-chakra-balancing/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:39:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=579</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Siem Reap Reiki and Prana Healing. Chakra Balancing PRANA CHAKRA &#38; SPIRITUAL ENERGY THERAPY Therapists All therapists are qualified and certified oneumatherapists trained by well known author of books on spirituality East and West, Jean du Plessis. Jean is our resident instructor in spiritual energy therapy. He lives in Siem Reap, Cambodia for most of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3>Siem Reap Reiki and Prana Healing. Chakra Balancing</h3>



<h3>PRANA CHAKRA &amp; SPIRITUAL ENERGY THERAPY</h3>



<h2><strong>Therapists</strong></h2>



<p>All therapists are qualified and certified oneumatherapists trained by well known author of books on spirituality East and West, Jean du Plessis.</p>



<p><strong>Jean</strong> is our resident instructor in spiritual energy therapy. He lives in Siem Reap, Cambodia for most of the year.</p>



<p><strong>Adele</strong> is a professional meditation instructor and pneumatherapist with more than 20-years experience in applying spiritual energy therapy.</p>



<p><strong>Steffi</strong> is a professional pneumatherapist, as well as a seasoned and highly educated councellor.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>We Test Chakra Energy</h2>



<ul><li>Before a session we chack chakra energies, meridian energies, dosha pulses and YinYang energies.&nbsp;</li><li>We will correct all energies possible within the scope of this Prana Reiki session</li><li>You will be advised if there is anything you should know about managing your spiritual energies</li></ul>



<h2>Duration and Price of a Reiki Prana Healing Session</h2>



<ul><li>How long does it take:  <strong>30-45 min</strong></li><li>When:  <strong>By appointment</strong></li><li>Where:  <strong>Siem Reap Wayist Center</strong> &#8211; see <a rel="noreferrer noopener" href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Wayist+Spiritual+Retreat/@13.3703347,103.865426,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x58935658e03e4579" target="_blank">Location</a></li><li><em>For more information</em>, please CONTACT US via <a class="" href="mailto:sr@wayist.com">sr@wayist.com</a> or <a href="tel:+85577804814">phone/ WhatsApp +85577804814</a></li><li>Complimentary Karman Meditation and Heart Sutra Mantra Meditation on day of visit, or during the following week (no cash value)</li></ul>



<h2><strong>About the Soul</strong></h2>



<p><strong>A soul, is a subtle energy body</strong> that consists of live energy matter and organs (chakras) of different types. We are souls. We are ancient, and we have had many opportunities to incarnate.</p>



<p>People know how to care for the human body in terms if nutrition, regular cleaning, and exercise &#8230; everyday maintenace. However, western people are not taught to care for their souls &#8211; regular cleaning, purifying, its nutrition and healing. That is what we do for you, <em><strong>we are a soul clinic</strong></em>, so-to-speak.</p>



<p><strong>A human body, is an organic body</strong> that consists of live organic matter and organs of different types. &nbsp;Human bodies are wondrous, yet they are fragile and do not last very long. The soul animates the body and it is affected by the body. You need a healthy soul to have a healthy body.</p>



<p><strong>The link between human body and the soul</strong>, is the human body-mind. The human mind is a subtle energy generated by the human brain. It’s lifespan and efficacy relies on the health and life of the brain. Body-minds try to deal with human experiences before the resulting wisdom is passed over to be permanently stored in soul minds.</p>



<p><strong>Soul Energy Therapy analyzes soul energies</strong> (often called, auras, kundalini, etc.). We determine whether conditions of the physical body, or human mind, negatively impact on one’s soul development-diagnosis.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="156" height="210" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/download1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-580"/></figure></div>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="325" height="365" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/kundalini-animated.gif" alt="" class="wp-image-296"/></figure></div>



<h2>What do we see?</h2>



<p>Captured in our four soul-minds (4 lower chakras) is the essence of who we are as individuals. We are the culmination of many lifetimes of experiences. Our soul energies create the ‘picture’ of what we ‘look’ like to other soul and spiritual beings. From a human perspective, looking at a soul is to see who we really are &#8211; the real person.</p>



<p>However, we need to explain that humans do not really see these energies with eyes, we sense. A large percentage of therapists sense auras most of the time when they are in therapeutic mode. Nevertheless, because auras change as soul moods change, the visible aura is not the most reliable diagnostic tool.</p>



<p>Soul energy animates the physical body. The physical body uses energy and that generates heat. To help, sometimes we make use of Infrared thermal imaging scans sensitive to 0.1<sup>0</sup>&nbsp;Celcius for certain tests. The scans on left shows before and after treatment &#8211; a pleasing result after two chakras were unblocked and prana flow restored to normal.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://wayist.com/images/infra2.png" alt="Infrared thermography spiritual chakra aura therapy"/></figure></div>



<p>We run energy tests, we do cross checks and double checks to finally get the full picture of the complex, multi-layered soul-person you are. A diagnostic session may have the look / feel of a combination of reiki, psychoanalysis, aromatherapy and touch therapies (massage / acupressure / reflexology).&nbsp;Treatment involves corrective actions which may involve chakra re-energizing, natural therapies, meridian work, prana correction, and if need be we guide on lifestyle changes, mental re-programming, physical interventions, and counselling.</p>



<p><strong>FYI</strong> &#8211; notice the breast scan to the right, below. It shows development of tumours in the left breast. Tumors demand increased blood flow and manifest a negative energy that a good therapist usually pics up.</p>



<p><em><strong>Please understand</strong></em> -we are not medical doctors and we do not do medical diagnoses. We will make you aware of issues if we notice them, but we are not medical practitioners, we are soul energy practitioners.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://wayist.com/images/themography-spiritual-counselling.jpg" alt="thermography spiritual counselling diagnostics breast scan siem reap wayist center"/></figure></div>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://wayist.com/images/reiki1.jpg" alt="prana energy and chakra healing clinic"/></figure></div>



<h2>Will I feel better after a session?</h2>



<p>Usually there is a feeling of wellness after a treatment. The sense of well-being is often a temporary symptomatic relief, because the root problem(s) lies deeper and needs long-term attention. Nevertheless, once a root problem is identified, one can usually continue along the healing path without the direct assistance of a therapist. The therapist’s task is to enable the patient on a healing path.</p>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<h2>Spiritual Energy Therapy</h2>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://wayist.com/images/eh-300x249.jpg" alt="Reiki Healing the Aura energy around the human body Cambodia"/></figure></div>



<p>Can spiritual energy therapy heal my physical and mental conditions?</p>



<p>You are spirit, the body that you inhabit relies on spiritual energy on several levels.</p>



<p>The human body is a complex natural system. It has its own natural mechanisms for homeostasis (regenerating and healing).</p>



<p>Spiritual energy animates the body, without which the body dies.</p>



<h2>When the spirit leaves, the body dies.</h2>



<p>We can state a very crude analogy. The body’s natural healing mechanisms may rely on spiritual energy as an intelligent robot relies on electricity. However, electricity is not system of software and mechanisms that cause homeostasis in the robot.</p>



<p>Will body and mental issues be properly resolved without spiritual energy? No, death of the body happens.</p>



<p>Will body and mental issues be properly resolved with only certain types of spiritual energy (when only some chakras are supplying energy)? This happens, but it is not ideal.</p>



<h2>If my spirit is sick, is there any reason to continue this incarnation?</h2>



<p>This is a popular question.</p>



<p>What you ask makes sense, because you are a spirit and the body with mind that you currently use is a very temporary tool for this phase.</p>



<p>If the body or mind is sick, you still learn and experience life; this incarnation is still valid and beneficial.</p>



<p>But, you reason, if you are sick, is it not better to go Home to heal and come back to earth-school another day?</p>



<p>Spirit can heal, even during an incarnation. The main reasons why you get sick is because of neglect, lack of maintenance and severe trauma that goes unattended. Ignorance makes people think to maintain only the body and its mind. Materialism and ego deludes people to think of themselves as fleshy animals, brains and blood with a national identity and a body adorned with brand name clothing, push-up bras and the lot—their selves, the spirit, is forgotten.</p>



<h2>What is spiritual energy therapy?</h2>



<p>Spiritual therapy starts with a diagnosis of energy flow in the various chakras. Your therapist would want to know about some lifestyle, mind and body-health issues that may impact, or be impacted by, your spiritual energy. Sometimes, questionnaires are used to assist in diagnosis.</p>



<p>Your aura energy is assessed. How far the aura energy extends, and the quality of the energy at certain areas. Aura energy is different around the body and is of diagnostic importance.<br>Spiritual therapy is aided by increased awareness of issues, if any.</p>



<p>Human spirits have seven spiritual minds, chakras, that are each tuned into a different spiritual energy frequency (of sorts).</p>



<p>For the spirit to be in good health, each chakra mind must be finely tuned, must send and receive its proper frequencies in clear energy without interruptions. This area is the focus of spiritual therapy.<br>Pneumatherapeutic tonics are often used to keep a particular chakra tuned and boost its energy output. This brings about spiritual homeostasis, and healing.</p>



<h2>Spiritual exercise and ‘nutrition’ is advised where required.</h2>



<p>Energy flows can be corrected when “congested” (to use an incorrect term) by means of Prana therapies that resemble Reiki.</p>



<p>In more serious cases, when a spirit is troubled or its health and fidelity is compromised by external influences, we may call on powerful spiritual forces (angels, gods, deities, or whatever names people use in different traditions) to help. These therapies are mostly very successful, and sometimes require follow-up visits. We understand these spiritual entities to be those often named as the Holy Spirit, the World Saviour, Bodhisattva Avalokiteshvara (Quanyin, Guanyin), for example.</p>



<h2>Chakra balancing and chakra energy restoration</h2>



<p>Technically, chakras are not balanced and do not go out of balance. A better term for westerners to describe what we do with Reiki and Prana Therapy would be, tuning and energizing chakras. We re-tune chakras that are not working optimally.</p>



<p>There are many reasons why chakras go out of tune (tune as is radio, or a television channel). The main reason why a chakra goes out of tune is because it is giving almost all of its energy to prevent a crisis in the human body or mind. It maintains only certain aspects of a sick human body, or it is helping the mind to deal with unhappiness, depression, lack of focus, delusion, lack of purpose, and whatnot. The chakra’s energies are needed by the organic body to produce a particular frequency of energy. This neglects the other frequencies that the chakra is supposed generate and feed to the soul, spirit and human body. Chakras are adept at this and recover quickly when the body or mind is healed of acute conditions. However, when chronic, the chakra can somehow sort-of “get stuck’ in that rut, tired, often depleting and in need of help.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/prana-reiki-chakra-balancing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>2</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Know your Karma</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/know-your-karma/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=know-your-karma</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/know-your-karma/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coaching & Healing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=573</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Know your Karma Our most popular service. Book ahead of time to avoid disappointment. Pre-paid bookings are prioritized in schedule, never moved or rescheduled. In this Chakra-Karma Guidance, we use the unique Soul-Chakra Personality Assessment TM developed by spirituality author and teacher, Jean du Plessis, to determine which of your chakra minds play a dominant role in your [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1 class="has-text-align-center">Know your Karma</h1>



<p class="has-text-align-center">Our most popular service. Book ahead of time to avoid disappointment. Pre-paid bookings are prioritized in schedule, never moved or rescheduled.</p>



<p class="has-text-align-center">In this Chakra-Karma Guidance, we use the unique <strong>Soul-Chakra Personality Assessment</strong> <sup>TM</sup> developed by spirituality author and teacher, Jean du Plessis, to determine which of your chakra minds play a dominant role in your soul personality, and if required, which spiritual therapies you may want to consider.</p>



<div class="wp-block-media-text alignwide is-stacked-on-mobile is-vertically-aligned-top" style="grid-template-columns:23% auto"><figure class="wp-block-media-text__media"><img loading="lazy" width="158" height="200" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/sapta_rsi_penerima_wahyu_veda.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-574"/></figure><div class="wp-block-media-text__content">
<p>With this therapeutic regimen, an analysis of your soul personality can help you to get to know your karma: The main reason why you incarnated in this lifetime, and what the main lessons you came to learn are.</p>



<p>You can also discover what the future may hold in terms of soul learning, and what the next major lessons on your path would be.</p>



<p>Your chakra energies are tested and the condition of your aura analyzed. You receive guidance in this regard to plan your future.</p>
</div></div>



<p>Learn more about the condition of your soul: What was the soul&#8217;s path up to now, and the major challenges that lie ahead on the way forward. Guided by Certified Soul-Chakra Personality Assessment&nbsp;TM&nbsp;counsellors.</p>



<p>You receive a PDF version of the graphic analysis by email on the day of your visist to the center.</p>



<p><strong>Included in the &#8216;Know your Karma&#8217; is a Chakra-Prana Reiki  session.</strong>  We clear energy channels (nadis and sushumna) and unblock chakras, and we do get to the root problems why your spiritual energy is not optimal. There is great physical, mental (emotional) and spiritual benefits in this SOUL MAINTENANCE program. Just as you take care of your physical body, you MUST maintain your soul body. <strong>Don&#8217;t neglect your Self. </strong></p>



<div class="wp-block-media-text alignwide has-media-on-the-right is-stacked-on-mobile is-vertically-aligned-top" style="grid-template-columns:auto 32%"><figure class="wp-block-media-text__media"><img loading="lazy" width="350" height="350" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/past_life_and_soul_path_reading_jean_du_plessis.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-575" srcset="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/past_life_and_soul_path_reading_jean_du_plessis.jpg 350w, https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/past_life_and_soul_path_reading_jean_du_plessis-300x300.jpg 300w, https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/past_life_and_soul_path_reading_jean_du_plessis-150x150.jpg 150w" sizes="(max-width: 350px) 100vw, 350px" /></figure><div class="wp-block-media-text__content">
<h2>Chakras</h2>



<p>The 7 chakras are spiritual energy centers, or rather soul and spirit minds located in our metaphysical bodies.  Chakras channel Prana (Universal Energy) both in and out of our soul minds and spiritual minds. </p>



<p>Each chakra communicates at a different spectrum of energy frequencies.&nbsp; &nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Chakras have ancient memories which form the personality of the soul.&nbsp; Chakras carry the sum of wisdom gathered over the soul&#8217;s ancient lifespan. &nbsp;</p>



<p>Captured in our four soul-minds (4 lower chakras) is the essence of who we are as individuals. We are the culmination of many lifetimes of experiences. &nbsp;The three spirit-minds (3 higher chakras) are the essence of our wisdom, and the spirit-mind chakras develop to a point where they start to dominate the soul-mind and soul chakras.</p>



<h2>Karma</h2>



<p>Karma will forcibly bring learning opportunities / lessons to us if we won’t do it by ourselves, yet we remain free to choose whatever course of action we will take. We are free to remain aware of learning opportunities in life, and we can decide whether or not to partake in them.&nbsp;</p>



<h2>Soul Path</h2>



<p>If you are sincere in your search, we can know your past life and soul path, your dharma and your duty for this life.&nbsp;</p>



<p>Is it possible that you are unhappy because you are not following your soul path?</p>



<p>What do you know about your soul mate, or your spiritual helper beings (angels?)?</p>



<h2>Time and Cost</h2>



<ul><li>How long does it take: 90-120 min.</li><li>When: By appointment</li><li>Where:&nbsp;<strong>Siem Reap Wayist Center</strong>&nbsp;&#8211; see&nbsp;<a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Wayist+Spiritual+Retreat/@13.3703347,103.865426,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x58935658e03e4579" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Location</a></li><li>For more information, please CONTACT US via&nbsp;<a class="" href="mailto:sr@wayist.com">sr@wayist.com</a>&nbsp;or&nbsp;<a href="tel:+85577804814">phone/ WhatsApp +85577804814</a></li></ul>



<p></p>
</div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/know-your-karma/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spiritual Energy Diagnosis</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-energy-diagnosis-2/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=spiritual-energy-diagnosis-2</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-energy-diagnosis-2/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:21:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coaching & Healing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=568</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Spiritual Body Diagnosis Spiritual Energy Diagnosis is&#160;the foundation of our&#160;clinical&#160;services While this page is written for our Siem Reap, Cambodia spiritual energy center, the same methods and ethics apply to other Pneumatherapy healing centers. Methodology Symptoms can have&#160;several causes. Symptoms can be caused either by,&#160;mental, psychological, physical, or spiritual conditions. It is therefore important&#160;to test, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>Spiritual Body Diagnosis</h1>



<h5>Spiritual Energy Diagnosis is&nbsp;the foundation of our&nbsp;clinical&nbsp;services</h5>



<p>While this page is written for our Siem Reap, Cambodia spiritual energy center, the same methods and ethics apply to other Pneumatherapy healing centers.</p>



<h4>Methodology</h4>



<p>Symptoms can have&nbsp;several causes. Symptoms can be caused either by,&nbsp;mental, psychological, physical, or spiritual conditions.</p>



<p>It is therefore important&nbsp;to test, check and recheck with different techniques and methods, to get a full and comprehensive&nbsp;picture of the status of the spirit/soul body and its energies.&nbsp;</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="196" height="371" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/5466.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-552" srcset="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/5466.jpg 196w, https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/5466-158x300.jpg 158w" sizes="(max-width: 196px) 100vw, 196px" /></figure></div>



<p>We test all chakras with two different methods.&nbsp;Meridian energy levels are traced and diagnosed.&nbsp;The flow of energy that&nbsp;Chinese Traditional Medicine refers to as&nbsp;Yin &amp; Yang energies is a&nbsp;bipolar Prana energy that flows through our physical and subtle bodies.&nbsp;Accupressure&nbsp;points are&nbsp;checked. Much data is gathered through information sharing, client therapist&nbsp;relationship. Prana and aura-field energies are checked.</p>



<p>The data is then correlated to determine exactly what it is that gives rise to an energy disturbance in a particular area.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/6c94851dbab1529a1a49aa8ef483a442.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-553" width="362" height="568"/></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>At this time a diagnosis can be made.</p>



<p>Appropriate therapeutic approaches and options are considered and explained.</p>



<h4>Best in the World?</h4>



<p>Is our system the best spiritual energy diagnostic regimen in the world? Most probably. At this time, our regimen is unsurpassed anywhere in the world. We are training other therapists, soon this system will become a new standard of care, and will not be so unique.</p>



<p></p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="226" height="223" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/pendulum-divination-spiritual-therapy-siem-reap.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-554"/></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>Our staff have advanced degrees and training in pneumatherapy. More importantly, we have been working in this field and continued studies in this field for the past thirty years. We have conducted almost 10,000&nbsp;counseling&nbsp;and healing sessions in more than seven countries on four continents.</p>



<p>Our academic studies at western universities and subsequent studies and clinical work&nbsp;in South East Asia over the past decades culminated in&nbsp;what is today most probably the most comprehensive spiritual diagnostic regimen in the world.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/infra-1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-556" width="274" height="248"/></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>It is true that under guidance of a single spiritual being (Holy Spirit, Avalokiteshvara, a deity, etc) one does not need additional diagnostic tools. And that is what Jean and Adele are aquinted with this. However, to teach and transfer skills in spiritual energy diagnoses, they&nbsp;developed this regimen that is suitable for anyone to master with practice,&nbsp;guidance and theoretical training. Jean and Adele teach this spiritual science at Prajnaparamita School of Pneumatherapy.</p>



<p>Regarding diagnosis, it is&nbsp;very&nbsp;important to have checks and balances in place, and in this regimen there are many. This directs us to&nbsp;uncover&nbsp;a full and comprehensive picture of the state of the soul.</p>



<h5>Touchy note</h5>



<p></p>



<p><strong>Please note</strong>: Some of the diagnostic and therapeutic methods&nbsp;involve touch. A therapist may need to touch your feet,head and body with her/his hands.&nbsp;A therapist may be&nbsp;of any gender. If you have a gender preference please state this upfront at time of making the appointment, we would gladly accommodate your requirements.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Clients who arrive at this session inebriated&nbsp;or under the influence of any mind altering drug (also antidepressants), may not&nbsp;get the most reliable results.</p>



<h5>Time and Cost</h5>



<p></p>



<p>How long it take: 60 to 90 min</p>



<p>Where:&nbsp;<strong>Siem Reap Wayist Center</strong>&nbsp;&#8211; see&nbsp;<a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Wayist+Spiritual+Retreat/@13.3703347,103.865426,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x58935658e03e4579" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Location</a></p>



<p><em>For more information</em>, please CONTACT US via&nbsp;<a class="" href="mailto:sr@wayist.com">sr@wayist.com</a>&nbsp;or&nbsp;<a href="tel:+85577804814">phone/ WhatsApp +85577804814</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-energy-diagnosis-2/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>人类生物群和灵魂能量治愈</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/%e4%ba%ba%e7%b1%bb%e7%94%9f%e7%89%a9%e7%be%a4%e5%92%8c%e7%81%b5%e9%ad%82%e8%83%bd%e9%87%8f%e6%b2%bb%e6%84%88/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=%25e4%25ba%25ba%25e7%25b1%25bb%25e7%2594%259f%25e7%2589%25a9%25e7%25be%25a4%25e5%2592%258c%25e7%2581%25b5%25e9%25ad%2582%25e8%2583%25bd%25e9%2587%258f%25e6%25b2%25bb%25e6%2584%2588</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/%e4%ba%ba%e7%b1%bb%e7%94%9f%e7%89%a9%e7%be%a4%e5%92%8c%e7%81%b5%e9%ad%82%e8%83%bd%e9%87%8f%e6%b2%bb%e6%84%88/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:20:30 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=567</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Human biome and soul energy cure人类生物群和灵魂能量治愈 Cambodian Human biota treatments stimulate immune mechanisms to maintain gut homeostasis and general health柬埔寨人类生物群治疗刺激免疫机制，以维持肠道稳态和一般健康 Cambodians live simple life with less toxins and more natural bacterial and human biota defences than any other Asian nation.与任何其他亚洲国家相比，柬埔寨人生活简单，毒素较少，天然细菌和人类生物群较多。 Microbes are carefully harvested from healthy certified individuals and transferred to the patient.从健康的认证个体中仔细收获微生物并转移给患者。 This happens [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3>Human biome and soul energy cure<br>人类生物群和灵魂能量治愈</h3>



<h4>Cambodian Human biota treatments stimulate immune mechanisms to maintain gut homeostasis and general health<br>柬埔寨人类生物群治疗刺激免疫机制，以维持肠道稳态和一般健康</h4>



<p>Cambodians live simple life with less toxins and more natural bacterial and human biota defences than any other Asian nation.<br>与任何其他亚洲国家相比，柬埔寨人生活简单，毒素较少，天然细菌和人类生物群较多。</p>



<p>Microbes are carefully harvested from healthy certified individuals and transferred to the patient.<br>从健康的认证个体中仔细收获微生物并转移给患者。<br><br>This happens on-site.<br>这是在诊所实时完成的。<br><br>No freezing or drying or transport of microbes is allowed.<br>不允许冷冻或干燥或运输微生物，它们无法存活。</p>



<p>Almost all human microbes will die when in contact with oxygen or light.<br>当暴露于氧气或光照时，几乎所有人类微生物都会死亡。</p>



<p>For that reason, we do on-site, real-time transfers.<br>出于这个原因，我们正在实时移动，从捐赠者到患者。</p>



<p>Donors are carefully selected, medically screened.<br>捐赠者经过精心挑选并通过药物筛选。</p>



<p>Treatments are for skin, mouth, small intestine, colon, vaginal and anal. You order what you need.<br>治疗适用于皮肤，口腔，小肠，结肠，阴道和肛门。 你订购了你需要的东西。</p>



<p>We guarantee confidentiality and privacy.<br>我们保证机密性和隐私。</p>



<p>Patient can see the donor.<br>患者可以看到捐赠者。</p>



<p>Receive the healthy bacteria, immunity and body chemistry of strong, healthy Cambodian donors.<br>接受强壮，健康的柬埔寨捐赠者的健康细菌，免疫力和身体化学。</p>



<p>Reports claim that they were cured from high blood pressure, ulcers, irratable bowel syndrome, bloating, low sex drive, impotence, vaginal dryness and atrophy, loss of energy, mental problems, depression, skin problems and low immune system.<br>报告称，他们治愈了高血压，溃疡，肠易激综合征，腹胀，性欲低下，阳痿，阴道干涩，精力减退，精神问题，抑郁，皮肤问题和免疫系统低下。</p>



<p>Our treatment is unique and suitable for everyone.<br>Our therapist Dr. Jean du Plessis (PnD, DDiv) is very qualified. Dr. Jean is not a doctor. He is a soul energy therapist, a spiritual energy therapist and a spiritual tradition teacher. He is a famous spiritual energy therapist in Hong Kong, Vietnam, Canada and the United States. He is the author of several books and training courses.</p>



<h2>我们的治疗非常独特，适合每个人。</h2>



<p><br>我们的治疗师Jean du Plessis博士（PnD，DDiv）非常合格。 Jean博士不是医生，他是一个灵魂能量治疗师，精神能量治疗师和精神传统的老师。 他是香港，越南，加拿大和美国着名的精神能量治疗师。 他是几本书籍和培训课程的作者。</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-medium"><img loading="lazy" width="270" height="300" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Human-Microbiome-270x300.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-569"/></figure></div>



<p>Happy people generally don&#8217;t get sick. Happy people have healthier genes. If we share their deep energy and biota, young, healthy, happy people can heal us.<br>快乐的人一般不会生病。 快乐的人有更健康的基因。 如果我们分享他们的深层能量和生物群，年轻，健康，快乐的人可以治愈我们。</p>



<p>This is not a medical procedure. No needles and no medications. We are not medical professionals. We can not tell if a therapy is safe for you, or if it will work for you. You must decide. Speak to your doctor.<br>这不是医疗程序。 没针，也没有药物。 我们不是医疗专业人士。 我们无法判断一种疗法对您是否安全，或者它是否适合您。 你必须决定。 跟你的医生说。</p>



<p>Our therapy makes you share in the microbe health of a carefully selected, clean, healthy young Cambodian woman or man.<br>我们的疗法让您分享精心挑选，清洁，健康的柬埔寨年轻女性或男性的微生物健康状况。</p>



<p>Therapy is available for entire body, inside and out. Therapy is also available for only the gut, or the skin, or vagina.<br>整个身体，内部和外部都可以使用治疗。 治疗也仅适用于肠道，皮肤或阴道。</p>



<p>For sexual health, we suggest therapy for the entire body.<br>对于性健康，我们建议对整个身体进行治疗。</p>



<p>For low energy and depression, the only therapy is for entire body immune system booster.<br>对于低能量和抑郁症，推荐的疗法是全身免疫系统助推器。</p>



<p>No chemicals. No medicine.<br>没有化学品。 没有西药。</p>



<p>Full soul energy healing is performed. Negative energies are removed. Clean, positive energy is restored. All chakras are balanced.<br>完成灵魂能量疗法。 消除负能量。 清洁，积极的能量回收。 所有的脉轮都是平衡的。</p>



<p>We can prepare certain remedies for patients to take home with them. Human biome infused remedies are used when required. Every remedy is unique.<br>我们可以为患者准备一些补救措施，带回家。 在需要时使用人类生物群落注入的补救措施。 每种补救措施都是独一无二</p>



<h2>TIME and COST<br><strong>时间和成本</strong></h2>



<p>Can only be made through an appointment. No appointment, we can&#8217;t treat anyone. We also need to carefully prepare donors before then.<br>只能通过预约。 没有约会，我们不能对待任何人。 我们还需要在此之前仔细准备捐助者。</p>



<p>Instructions how to prepare for an appointment is given when appointment is sceduled.<br>安排预约时，将提供如何准备预约的说明。</p>



<p>Our therapies take several hours. Plan to spend almost one full day at our clinic.<br>You need to prepare before appointment. Live very clean for three days after appointment.</p>



<p>我们的治疗需要几个小时。 我计划在诊所度过将近一整天的时间。<br>您需要在预约前做好准备。 预约后保持清洁三天。</p>



<p>#1. Standard Therapy: USD $980<br>Standard biota transfer therapy includes energy therapy and careful transfer of the type of biome you choose. All types of biomes are included in the price, but you decide what you don&#8217;t need.</p>



<h2><br>#1. 标准治疗：980美元</h2>



<p>标准生物群系转移疗法包括能量治疗以及您选择的生物群系类型的仔细转移。 所有类型的生物群系都包含在价格中，但您决定了您不需要的东西。</p>



<p>#2. Deep Cleansing Infusion: USD $1,860<br>Some customers need the most thorough treatment in four days. The soul energy is restored. Qi deficiency is cured. Body is cleaned inside and outside to release toxins and old energy.<br>Then, over two days, from two different donors, the healthy biota is transferred into the body during four sessions. Plus the final test and observation of the day.</p>



<h2>#2. 深层清洁输液 : 1,860美元</h2>



<p>有些客户需要在四天内获得最彻底的治疗。 灵魂能量得到恢复。 气虚治愈。 内部和外部清洁身体以释放毒素和旧能量。<br>然后，在两天内，来自两个不同的捐赠者，健康的生物群将在四个疗程期间转移到身体。 加上第二天的最终测试和观察。</p>



<p>Please note: Above therapies involve professional bare skin touch, light rubbing with oil and fluids, and depending on your selection may involve specialised small enema. Female staff are present but the therapist is male.<br>请注意：以上疗法涉及整个身体的专业裸露皮肤触感，轻轻摩擦油和液体，并根据您的选择可能涉及专门的小灌肠。女性工作人员在场，但治疗师是男性。</p>



<p>#3. For soul healing and Qi and mental energy healing only, the standard rate is $60 and time is 1 hour.</p>



<h2>#3. 仅用于灵魂治疗和气虚和精神能量治疗，标准费用为60美元，时间为1小时。</h2>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/%e4%ba%ba%e7%b1%bb%e7%94%9f%e7%89%a9%e7%be%a4%e5%92%8c%e7%81%b5%e9%ad%82%e8%83%bd%e9%87%8f%e6%b2%bb%e6%84%88/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>6</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>More about diagnosing spiritual energy</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/more-about-diagnosing-spiritual-energy/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=more-about-diagnosing-spiritual-energy</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/more-about-diagnosing-spiritual-energy/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:18:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coaching & Healing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=563</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Spiritual Energy Diagnosis and Therapy What is spiritual energy There is an energy that runs through the sub-atomic matter of all of creation. That energy directs all the minute parts in creation by telling it how to behave to function perfectly, as Creation intended. That is the energy we work with. Some call it Prana, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1 class="has-text-align-center">Spiritual Energy Diagnosis and Therapy</h1>



<h2>What is spiritual energy</h2>



<p>There is an energy that runs through the sub-atomic matter of all of creation. That energy directs all the minute parts in creation by telling it how to behave to function perfectly, as Creation intended. That is the energy we work with. Some call it Prana, some call it Qi, some just say Universal Energy.</p>



<p>The human spirit is a creature, we are spiritual beings (temporarily incarnated, on Earth). Our Father in Heaven is the wisest, most senior spiritual being known to humankind, also a created being, yet, a god to us. It is this energy that makes us our spiritual bodies, that we work with in pneumatherapy.</p>



<p>Spiritual energy is absolutely not part of the Earthly electromagnetic energy spectrum; it has nothing to do with the gross energies of the three dimensional worlds. Therefore, if anyone claims to be able to take a photograph or ‘scan’ of the spirit, or claims to actually see (with her/his eyes) a chakra or soul or spiritual energy, s/he is misinformed or is misleading.</p>



<p>Spiritual energy can be sensed by souls, can be directed (to an extent) by another spirit, but it cannot yet be recorded by three-dimensional world tools.</p>



<p>We can sense the presence of the Divine in all things when our heart chakras are trained to do so. We can sense the presence of spiritual beings (the Lord, angels, deva, devata, etc.) and we can communicate (or at least receive communication) from them when we have tuned our chakra receivers on their spiritual energy frequencies.</p>



<h2>How are diagnoses of spiritual energy done</h2>



<p>Your therapist is trained and equipped to sense your spiritual energy, often called your aura or chakra energies.</p>



<p>Therapists may use tools to help direct their sensing, but these tools are almost always simple, crude, devices that serve only to help the therapist to interpret things. I use a pendulum when convenient I had to work in a train, or (heck I hope never) in a bus I would use something else. Who or what moves the pendulum? Well, we are trained to not work with our own spiritual energy but with that of the client/patient and his/her angel or the spiritual presence of a spiritual being who cares about the healing of the patient. This is often rather intense for the therapist.</p>



<p>Therapists use several techniques, in succession, and compares the results with your own observations.</p>



<p>Relationship with the therapist plays a major role. Therapists are trained to step into relationship with your spiritual energy field, but if you relax and make your energies available, things go smoother and the therapeutic process is most effective.</p>



<h2>How do I prepare for a spiritual energy therapy session?</h2>



<p>Pneumatherapists do not make use of invasive techniques (needles, scalpels, insertions, or anywhere near genitalia, etc.). However, for the benefit of German, American and Canadian clients (who are the most touch-paranoid people on earth), please note that it is often necessary for someone to touch you in a therapeutic way.</p>



<p>You must mention if you are under the influence of drugs like alcohol or mind-altering medications, or drugs. More often than not, such a condition complicates matters.</p>



<p>Remove, or do not wear amulets, metals or jewelry of any nature. Some elements may have an effect of the interpretation of energy fields in and around the spiritual energy centers.</p>



<p>Relax, be yourself and share, share with your therapist. Your interaction with the therapist plays a big role in interpretation and understanding of your energies.</p>



<h2>Why should you have your spiritual energy diagnosed and maintained?</h2>



<p>People wash, feed and exercise their physical bodies because it is good stewardship and one must do due diligence maintenance on it.</p>



<p>You are not your physical body. It is on a temporary loan to you. You are an ancient spiritual being, your body is made of spiritual energy and you have several spiritual “organs” in a manner of speaking. To maintain, exercise and feed your true self, your ancient body, is the responsible thing to do. It just makes natural sense.</p>



<h2>Spiritual energy problems can lead to mental problems and/or physical ailments.</h2>



<p>On the other hand, mental problems and/or physical ailments often negatively impact spiritual health because the spirit is working overtime, often for years, to try and maintain the soul and physical body to make the most of this reincarnation opportunity.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/more-about-diagnosing-spiritual-energy/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spiritual Healing</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-healing/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=spiritual-healing</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-healing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:17:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coaching & Healing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=559</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[What spiritual Healing is not Spiritual healing is not science Any attempt to explain Spiritual Healing in scientific terms will fail, and rightfully so. It is nothing less than folly to use the terms and laws of one field to explain things of an altogether different field—likewise, no-one should try to explain the Mechanisms of [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3 class="has-text-align-center">What spiritual Healing is not</h3>



<div class="wp-block-media-text alignwide is-stacked-on-mobile is-vertically-aligned-top" style="grid-template-columns:43% auto"><figure class="wp-block-media-text__media"><img loading="lazy" width="424" height="283" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Reiki.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-561" srcset="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Reiki.jpg 424w, https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Reiki-300x200.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 424px) 100vw, 424px" /></figure><div class="wp-block-media-text__content">
<h3><strong>Spiritual healing is not science</strong></h3>



<p><strong>Any attempt to explain Spiritual Healing in scientific terms will fail</strong>, and rightfully so. It is nothing less than folly to use the terms and laws of one field to explain things of an altogether different field—likewise, no-one should try to explain the Mechanisms of Music by using the jargon, references and laws of the field of International Politics, and insist that Mechanisms of Music can be understood in terms of International Politics. There may some correlations, some causal factors, but the one can never be explained, studied and practised in terms of the laws and nature of the other.</p>



<p>In this vein,&nbsp;<strong>several ‘teachers’ of Yogi Philosophy are wrong</strong>&nbsp;when they perpetuate a language and mind-set in which they speak of the higher Tantras, Kundalini and Prana as &#8220;Yoga Technology&#8221;. The term “technology” applies to the field of Science. Technology is defined as: &#8220;<em>the application of scientific knowledge for practical purposes, especially in industry</em>&#8220;. Yogic and higher Spiritual Philosophy, and spiritual energy healing belongs to the field of meta-physics and can never be studied and applied as a science or one of its technologies.</p>
</div></div>



<h2>What is Spiritual Healing</h2>



<p>Spiritual Energy animates the human body. Without this energy, when the soul leaves the human body, the body dies. It is this Energy with which we work to heal the holistic person (body, mind and soul), not only the ailment in the physical body.</p>



<p>Spiritual Energy keeps the body alive and energizes its natural homeostasis, its ability to heal and repair itself.</p>



<p>Moreover, under good conditions spiritual energy repairs DNA and RNA, reprograms the human body’s mind, animates the body&#8217;s mechanisms to do what it had always done (fight off pathogens, viruses, cancers, cell and nerve damage) and brings about healing that goes beyond what a single medical regime can accomplish.</p>



<p>Allopathic (modern) medicine makes use of chemicals that target mostly single functions inside a human body. It takes another doctor, from another discipline to target the human mind, psychology. Then, the patient will most prabably not consult a spiritual doctor to heal the spiritual condition. Few people go to the trouble to see three practitioners for a single ailment.</p>



<h2>About the Pneumatherapist</h2>



<p>The Pneumatherapist or Doctor of Spiritual Energy targets the holistic person via the channel of higher authority in the human’s constitution, that of spiritual energy.</p>



<p>Pneumatherapists undergo many years of study and internship. Pneumatherapists make use of a variety of techniques known by different names all over the world. Some of the names of generic healing tools that one may immediately recognize, for example, will be: Reiki, Prana Therapy, Chakra Energy Healing, QiGong, Qi-therapy, Prayer, Channeling, Acupressure, Meridian Therapy, Touch Therapy, Holistic Massage, Distant Healing, Contact Healing, Bio-energy Healing, and Acupuncture.By:&nbsp;<a href="https://wayist.com/index.php/component/content/?id=130&amp;Itemid=1683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Jean du Plessis</a>, Nov 2016.</p>



<p><strong>Jean</strong>&nbsp;is a prominent spiritual healer and author of several books.</p>



<p><strong>Adele</strong>&nbsp;is a compassionate and sought after spiritual healer.</p>



<p><strong>Steffi</strong>&nbsp;is a insightful and caring spiritual healer.</p>



<p>Clients from around the world visit The Spiritual Energy Center in Siem Reap, Cambodia.NOTES:</p>



<ul><li>Science is defined as “the intellectual and practical activity encompassing the systematic study of the structure and behaviour of the&nbsp;physical and natural world&nbsp;through observation and experiment”.</li><li>Spiritual healing is incomprehensible by the intellectual (in)capacity of the human animal’s organic brain, mostly due to its inability to comprehend metaphysics and supernatural things.</li><li>Spiritual healing and its energies and mechanisms of healing mostly fall outside the spectrum of the physical and natural world—which is the domain of science. Spiritual healing falls within the domain of&nbsp;meta-physics, or the super-natural world of the soul, spirit, angels and gods.</li><li>Scientific tools of observation and measurement are effective only in the natural world with its gross energies (electromagnetic spectrum) and material manifestations. These tools and devices (radio, photo, x-ray, microwave, etc.) are incapable of detecting spiritual energies. Soul beings, however, detect spiritual energies all the time, making use of soul ‘tools’ and faculties often called minor chakras in the aura.</li></ul>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-healing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>រកប្រាក់បានរហូតដល់ 60 ដុល្លារក្នុងមួយថ្ងៃ</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%80%e1%9e%94%e1%9f%92%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%b6%e1%9e%80%e1%9f%8b%e1%9e%94%e1%9e%b6%e1%9e%93%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%a0%e1%9e%bc%e1%9e%8f%e1%9e%8a%e1%9e%9b%e1%9f%8b-60-%e1%9e%8a%e1%9e%bb%e1%9e%9b/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=%25e1%259e%259a%25e1%259e%2580%25e1%259e%2594%25e1%259f%2592%25e1%259e%259a%25e1%259e%25b6%25e1%259e%2580%25e1%259f%258b%25e1%259e%2594%25e1%259e%25b6%25e1%259e%2593%25e1%259e%259a%25e1%259e%25a0%25e1%259e%25bc%25e1%259e%258f%25e1%259e%258a%25e1%259e%259b%25e1%259f%258b-60-%25e1%259e%258a%25e1%259e%25bb%25e1%259e%259b</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%80%e1%9e%94%e1%9f%92%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%b6%e1%9e%80%e1%9f%8b%e1%9e%94%e1%9e%b6%e1%9e%93%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%a0%e1%9e%bc%e1%9e%8f%e1%9e%8a%e1%9e%9b%e1%9f%8b-60-%e1%9e%8a%e1%9e%bb%e1%9e%9b/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:13:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=551</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Human immunity and soul healingភាពស៊ាំរបស់មនុស្សនិងការព្យាបាលថាមពលព្រលឹង Earn money by donating your body chemistry.រកប្រាក់បានដោយការបរិច្ចាគគីមីសាស្ត្ររាងកាយរបស់អ្នក។ ការរស់នៅរាប់លាននាក់រស់នៅក្នុងនិងលើខ្លួនរបស់អ្នក។ វាជួយអ្នកអោយមានសុខភាពល្អ។ If you have good health and live a clean life. Your body chemistry can treat patients.ប្រសិនបើអ្នកមានសុខភាពល្អនិងរស់នៅក្នុងជីវិតស្អាតស្អំ។ គីមីវិទ្យារាងកាយរបស់អ្នកអាចព្យាបាលអ្នកជំងឺ។ This is not a medical procedure. No pain. No injections.នេះមិនមែនជានីតិវិធីវេជ្ជសាស្រ្តទេ។ គ្មាន​ការឈឺចាប់។ មិនមានការចាក់ថ្នាំឡើយ។ We collect bacteria from the inside of the body and the outer.យើងប្រមូលបាក់តេរីពីខាងក្នុងនៃរាងកាយនិងខាងក្រៅ។ [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3>Human immunity and soul healing<br>ភាពស៊ាំរបស់មនុស្សនិងការព្យាបាលថាមពលព្រលឹង</h3>



<h3>Earn money by donating your body chemistry.<br>រកប្រាក់បានដោយការបរិច្ចាគគីមីសាស្ត្ររាងកាយរបស់អ្នក។</h3>



<p>ការរស់នៅរាប់លាននាក់រស់នៅក្នុងនិងលើខ្លួនរបស់អ្នក។ វាជួយអ្នកអោយមានសុខភាពល្អ។</p>



<p>If you have good health and live a clean life. Your body chemistry can treat patients.<br>ប្រសិនបើអ្នកមានសុខភាពល្អនិងរស់នៅក្នុងជីវិតស្អាតស្អំ។ គីមីវិទ្យារាងកាយរបស់អ្នកអាចព្យាបាលអ្នកជំងឺ។</p>



<p>This is not a medical procedure. No pain. No injections.<br>នេះមិនមែនជានីតិវិធីវេជ្ជសាស្រ្តទេ។ គ្មាន​ការឈឺចាប់។ មិនមានការចាក់ថ្នាំឡើយ។</p>



<p>We collect bacteria from the inside of the body and the outer.<br>យើងប្រមូលបាក់តេរីពីខាងក្នុងនៃរាងកាយនិងខាងក្រៅ។</p>



<p>Please come for an interview. Everything will be explained.<br>សូមមកសំភាសន៍។ អ្វីគ្រប់យ៉ាងនឹងត្រូវបានពន្យល់។</p>



<p>If approved. You get your setup instructions and appointments a week later.<br>ប្រសិនបើមានការយល់ព្រម។ អ្នកទទួលការណែនាំអំពីការរៀបចំនិងការណាត់ជួបរបស់អ្នកមួយសប្តាហ៍ក្រោយមក។</p>



<h4>During the month of June. We need applications only from healthy females age 30 to 45.<br>អំឡុងខែមិថុនា។ យើងគ្រាន់តែត្រូវការកម្មវិធីពីស្ត្រីដែលមានសុខភាពល្អដែលមានអាយុពី 30 ទៅ 45 ឆ្នាំប៉ុណ្ណោះ។</h4>



<p>Important. Our technicians speak only English. You must be able to understand English.<br>សំខាន់។ អ្នកបច្ចេកទេសរបស់យើងនិយាយតែភាសាអង់គ្លេសប៉ុណ្ណោះ។ អ្នកត្រូវតែយល់ភាសាអង់គ្លេស។</p>



<p>Our customers are outside of Cambodia. We guarantee confidentiality.<br>អតិថិជនរបស់យើងគឺចេញពីប្រទេសកម្ពុជា។ យើងធានាថាជាការសម្ងាត់។</p>



<p>You can earn between $30 and $60 for an appointment, depending on what the customer needs.<br>អ្នកអាចរកប្រាក់ចំណូលបានពី 30 ទៅ 60 ដុល្លារសម្រាប់ការណាត់ជួបមួយអាស្រ័យលើអ្វីដែលអតិថិជនត្រូវការ។</p>



<p>Contact tel# 619 09956 for an interview. Thank you for using English.<br>ទាក់ទង 619 09956 សម្រាប់ការសំភាសន៍។ សូមអរគុណចំពោះការប្រើប្រាស់ភាសាអង់គ្លេស។</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%80%e1%9e%94%e1%9f%92%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%b6%e1%9e%80%e1%9f%8b%e1%9e%94%e1%9e%b6%e1%9e%93%e1%9e%9a%e1%9e%a0%e1%9e%bc%e1%9e%8f%e1%9e%8a%e1%9e%9b%e1%9f%8b-60-%e1%9e%8a%e1%9e%bb%e1%9e%9b/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spiritual Energy Diagnosis</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-energy-diagnosis/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=spiritual-energy-diagnosis</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-energy-diagnosis/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 14:12:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coaching & Healing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=549</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Spiritual Body Diagnosis Spiritual Energy Diagnosis is&#160;the foundation of our&#160;clinical&#160;services While this page is written for our Siem Reap, Cambodia spiritual energy center, the same methods and ethics apply to other Pneumatherapy healing centers. Methodology Symptoms can have&#160;several causes. Symptoms can be caused either by,&#160;mental, psychological, physical, or spiritual conditions. It is therefore important to test, [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h1>Spiritual Body Diagnosis</h1>



<h5>Spiritual Energy Diagnosis is&nbsp;the foundation of our&nbsp;clinical&nbsp;services</h5>



<p>While this page is written for our Siem Reap, Cambodia spiritual energy center, the same methods and ethics apply to other Pneumatherapy healing centers.</p>



<h4>Methodology</h4>



<p>Symptoms can have&nbsp;several causes. Symptoms can be caused either by,&nbsp;mental, psychological, physical, or spiritual conditions.</p>



<p>It is therefore important to test, check and recheck with different techniques and methods, to get a full and comprehensive picture of the status of the spirit/soul body and its energies. </p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="196" height="371" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/5466.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-552" srcset="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/5466.jpg 196w, https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/5466-158x300.jpg 158w" sizes="(max-width: 196px) 100vw, 196px" /></figure></div>



<p>We test all chakras with two different methods.&nbsp;Meridian energy levels are traced and diagnosed.&nbsp;The flow of energy that&nbsp;Chinese Traditional Medicine refers to as&nbsp;Yin &amp; Yang energies is a&nbsp;bipolar Prana energy that flows through our physical and subtle bodies.&nbsp;Accupressure&nbsp;points are&nbsp;checked. Much data is gathered through information sharing, client therapist&nbsp;relationship. Prana and aura-field energies are checked.</p>



<p>The data is then correlated to determine exactly what it is that gives rise to an energy disturbance in a particular area.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/6c94851dbab1529a1a49aa8ef483a442.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-553" width="362" height="568"/></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>At this time a diagnosis can be made.</p>



<p>Appropriate therapeutic approaches and options are considered and explained.</p>



<h4>Best in the World?</h4>



<p>Is our system the best spiritual energy diagnostic regimen in the world? Most probably. At this time, our regimen is unsurpassed anywhere in the world. We are training other therapists, soon this system will become a new standard of care, and will not be so unique.</p>



<p></p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="226" height="223" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/pendulum-divination-spiritual-therapy-siem-reap.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-554"/></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>Our staff have advanced degrees and training in pneumatherapy. More importantly, we have been working in this field and continued studies in this field for the past thirty years. We have conducted almost 10,000 counseling and healing sessions in more than seven countries on four continents.</p>



<p>Our academic studies at western universities and subsequent studies and clinical work in South East Asia over the past decades culminated in what is today most probably the most comprehensive spiritual diagnostic regimen in the world.</p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter size-large is-resized"><img loading="lazy" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/infra-1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-556" width="274" height="248"/></figure></div>



<p></p>



<p>It is true that under guidance of a single spiritual being (Holy Spirit, Avalokiteshvara, a deity, etc) one does not need additional diagnostic tools. And that is what Jean and Adele are aquinted with this. However, to teach and transfer skills in spiritual energy diagnoses, they&nbsp;developed this regimen that is suitable for anyone to master with practice,&nbsp;guidance and theoretical training. Jean and Adele teach this spiritual science at Prajnaparamita School of Pneumatherapy.</p>



<p>Regarding diagnosis, it is&nbsp;very&nbsp;important to have checks and balances in place, and in this regimen there are many. This directs us to&nbsp;uncover&nbsp;a full and comprehensive picture of the state of the soul.</p>



<h5>Touchy note</h5>



<p></p>



<p><strong>Please note</strong>: Some of the diagnostic and therapeutic methods&nbsp;involve touch. A therapist may need to touch your feet,head and body with her/his hands.&nbsp;A therapist may be&nbsp;of any gender. If you have a gender preference please state this upfront at time of making the appointment, we would gladly accommodate your requirements.&nbsp;&nbsp;</p>



<p>Clients who arrive at this session inebriated&nbsp;or under the influence of any mind altering drug (also antidepressants), may not&nbsp;get the most reliable results.</p>



<h5>Time and Cost</h5>



<p></p>



<p>How long it take: 60 to 90 min</p>



<p>Where:&nbsp;<strong>Siem Reap Wayist Center</strong>&nbsp;&#8211; see&nbsp;<a href="https://www.google.com/maps/place/Wayist+Spiritual+Retreat/@13.3703347,103.865426,15z/data=!4m2!3m1!1s0x0:0x58935658e03e4579" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Location</a></p>



<p><em>For more information</em>, please CONTACT US via&nbsp;<a class="" href="mailto:sr@wayist.com">sr@wayist.com</a>&nbsp;or&nbsp;<a href="tel:+85577804814">phone/ WhatsApp +85577804814</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-energy-diagnosis/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Spiritual Life Coaching</title>
		<link>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-life-coaching/?utm_source=rss&#038;utm_medium=rss&#038;utm_campaign=spiritual-life-coaching</link>
					<comments>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-life-coaching/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[adminenergy]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2020 13:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Coaching & Healing]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://wayist.com/?p=537</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Individual spiritual counselling sessions Individual Spiritual Counselling Who benefits most from spiritual counselling with a professional pneumatherapist (pneuma is Gk. for spirit)? Often-times, spirituality, cultural conditioning and religious dogma comes in a mixed bag of things than can create emotional conditions which negatively impact on soul development and spiritual harmony. Rediscover your innate, natural spirituality that [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<h3><a href="http://wayist.com/coaching-healing/individual-spiritual-counselling-sessions">Individual spiritual counselling sessions</a></h3>



<h1>Individual Spiritual Counselling</h1>



<p></p>



<h3>Who benefits most from spiritual counselling with a professional pneumatherapist (<em>pneuma</em> is Gk. for spirit)?</h3>



<p></p>



<p>Often-times, spirituality, cultural conditioning and religious dogma comes in a mixed bag of things than can create emotional conditions which negatively impact on soul development and spiritual harmony.</p>



<p>Rediscover your innate, natural spirituality that has served you well over many past lives. Rediscover your happiness and your individual path to spiritual health &#8211; and how to either embrace or put behind you the religious and cultural influences of this life.</p>



<div class="wp-block-media-text alignwide has-media-on-the-right is-stacked-on-mobile is-vertically-aligned-top" style="grid-template-columns:auto 32%"><figure class="wp-block-media-text__media"><img loading="lazy" width="500" height="500" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Healing1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-544" srcset="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Healing1.jpg 500w, https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/Healing1-480x480.jpg 480w" sizes="(min-width: 0px) and (max-width: 480px) 480px, (min-width: 481px) 500px, 100vw" /></figure><div class="wp-block-media-text__content">
<p>A well rounded pneumatherapist will help you to make sense of the true issues, and help to separate the baggage of totem, taboo, and dogma from your true inherent spirituality that has served you so well, over many, many past lives. Discover your natural spirituality, and happiness—and how to make peace with, or put behind you the religious influences of this life.</p>



<p>Then, there are the outliers—people who are either atheist or being haunted or affected by ghosts or spells.</p>



<p>Whether you come from a Christian, Buddhist, Hindu or Daoist culture, Jean du Plessis is in a very good position to bring healing to your life. He is a trained Christian theologian and minister, an lifelong scholar and practitioner of Buddhist, Hindu and Daoist lore and rite. </p>



<p></p>
</div></div>



<h3>Do you have questions about theology, or the philosophy of a particular discipline?</h3>



<p>A well rounded professional with credentials in studies of World Religions can help.</p>



<p>What is the difference between soul, spirit and mind, and why do most writers and translators of Biblical text translate the original Greek <em>pneuma</em> (spirit), <em>psyche</em> (soul) and <em>nous</em> (mind) willy-nilly as soul / spirit without rhyme or reason? And the cherry on the cake—why are psychologists called soul doctors (psyche=soul), if they don’t believe in souls, but tell us it is all in the mind—and mind <em>nous</em>; they should be called nousologists,</p>



<div class="wp-block-media-text alignwide is-stacked-on-mobile" style="grid-template-columns:24% auto"><figure class="wp-block-media-text__media"><img loading="lazy" width="968" height="1024" src="https://wayist.com/wp-content/uploads/2020/05/bayon_150121_714abCrpHrd-2-968x1024.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-545"/></figure><div class="wp-block-media-text__content">
<p>mind doctors, not soul doctors. Learn how to undo this damage, so it stops interfering with your development of soul.</p>



<p>When it comes to ghosts, spells, superstitions and damaging hauntings—you need the help of someone with experience in countries ravaged by these issues—like Cambodia and Africa. Jean du Plessis has a home in Canada but nowadays lives in Siem Reap, most of the time. He lived in Africa for almost four decades.</p>
</div></div>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://wayist.com/2020/05/13/spiritual-life-coaching/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
